Guide to the Ellen McGowan Biddle Shipman papers, 1914-1946.
Shipman, Ellen McGowan Biddle papers, 1914-1946.
- Series IV. Project Files (Plans)
  - Mrs. James V. Forrestal (Map-case Folder 189)
    - Planting plan for residence at 17 Beekman Place (Map-case Folder 189)
  - Robert A. Frankie (Map-case Folder 190)
    Location: Llewlyn Park, New Jersey
    - Topographical survey of property (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Shryb planting plan to screen tennis court (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Construction plan of garden (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Construction plan of cutting garden (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Shrub planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Planting plan for flower garden - Sheet A and B (Map-case Folder 190)
  - Mrs. Christian De Waal (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Detail for tea house floor (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Construction details for wooden gate in south west wall (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Perennial planting plan (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Map of property (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Planting plan for green garden (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Sketch plan showing design for garden (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Construction details for north wall (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Construction details for lattice on north wall (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Sketch of gate (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Construction details for gates in north wall (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Detail of top of gate in south west wall (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Construction details for tea house door (Map-case Folder 190)
    - General construction plan for garden (Map-case Folder 190)
    - General grading plan (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Planting plan for area around front of house (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Bulb planting plan for garden (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Construction details for gate (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Construction details for wall fountain in south west wall (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Cornice details of tea house (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Elevations of tea house (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Construction details for foundations of tea house (Map-case Folder 190)
    - Patterns of brick paving in garden paths (Map-case Folder 190)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Lyman Dyer (Map-case Folder 191)
    - Planting plan for flowering trees (Map-case Folder 191)
    - Planting plan for front of house (Map-case Folder 191)
    - Design plan for gardens (Map-case Folder 191)
  - Mrs. J.F. Dickson (Map-case Folder 191)
    - Construction plan for flower garden (2 Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 191)
    - Design plan (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 191)
  - Mr. and Mrs. John Green (Map-case Folder 192)
    - List of plants (Map-case Folder 192)
    - Planting plan for white garden (Map-case Folder 192)
    - Planting plan for camellia garden (Map-case Folder 192)
  - Greening Nurseries (Map-case Folder 192)
    Location: Monroe, Michigan
    - Plan showing existing conditions (Map-case Folder 192)
    - Desing and planting plan (Map-case Folder 192)
  - Mrs. Edwin Gould (Map-case Folder 192)
    - Shrub planting plan for around picking garden (Map-case Folder 192)
    - Construction plan for picking garden (Map-case Folder 192)
    - Planting plan for picking garden (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 192)
    - Standards planting plan for picking garden (Map-case Folder 192)
    - Planting plan for east half of picking garden (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 192)
    - Planting plan for east half of picking garden (Black and White) (Map-case Folder 192)
  - Mrs. Robert A. Gardner (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Perennial planting plan for pear tree border (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Plan of additional planting for terrace (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Bulb planting plan for pear tree border (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Planting plan of paved court (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Design for kitchen garden and greenhouse (Map-case Folder 193)
    - General tree and shrub planting plan (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Planting plan for forecourt (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Tree and shrub planting plan for boundary (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Plan of topography (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 193)
  - Mrs. Edward Goldthorpe (Map-case Folder 193)
    - General plan (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Construction details for pool and steps (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Contour and topographic map (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 193)
  - Mr. Bradley Gaylord (Map-case Folder 193)
    Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Planting plan for screen against southwest wall (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Planting plan for rock outcrop and the rill (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Section J-J, showing rock outcropping (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Construction plan for rill and path (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Preliminary design plan (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Construction plan for stone seat in rookery (Map-case Folder 193)
    - Bulb planting plan in rock outcrop (Map-case Folder 193)
  - West End Methodist Episcopal Church (Map-case Folder 194)
    - Plot plan (Blueprint) (Map-case Folder 194)
    - North, East, South and West elevations (Blueprints), 1929 (Map-case Folder 194)
      Mayers, Murray, and Phillip, Architect
  - Unlabeled garden plan (Map-case Folder 194)
  - J. Watson Webb (Map-case Folder 198)
    - 4 photocopies of plans, c. 1919 (Map-case Folder 198)
  - Howard Heinz (Box 14)
    Location: None given
    - Grass, walk and fountain sketch (matted) (Box 14)
    - Arch "A" sketch (matted) (Box 14)
    - Mill Stone sketch (matted) (Box 14)
    - Door sketch (matted) (Box 14)
    - Dipping Well sketch (matted) (Box 14)
    - Hooded seat sketch (matted) (Box 14)
    - Play house sketch (matted) (Box 14)
    - Arch "B" sketch (matted) (Box 14)